# JULIÁN RAMOS

• Web Developer •

## ABOUT ME

My target is to train as a professional in a company that values my skills and performance. Organized, proactive, quick to solve problems and a good presence.

I have been developing pages for 3 years with different technologies, I made them full stack but I prefer the front-end section. I am always studying to keep improving.

#### Portfolio:

https://julianramos42.github.io/Portfolio/

## EDUCATION

2022 • Universidad Tecnológica Nacional - Informatic Engineer

2022 • Codo a Codo 4.0 - Web Developer FullStack Python

2017 • Instituto Inmaculada - Bachelor in Economics and Administration

## EXPERIENCE

#### 2022 - 2023 Technical Support

Phone Operator in Cat Technologies

- In charge of attend the calls of Personal Flow clients
- Solve the doubts, queries and technical problems of these clients
- Organization of technical services

## 2017 - 2022 Management of Drugstore

Cashier, Stocker and Customer Service

- Responsible for attend customer needs
- Opening and closing of cash register
- · Organization of the purchase of inputs and order them in their respective place

# 2017 - 2017 Customer Service

Cashier and Customer Service in LA IMPRENTA

• Responsible for attend customer needs

# SKILLS

I work with no problem this technologies, HTML,CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript with Vue.Js, Git, etc, i recommend visiting my portfolio so you can also see my work.

# CONTACT

**Celphone:** +54 9 1150234561 **Email:** julianete4@gmail.com

Age: 22 años

Location: Almirante Brown, Claypole